Guide to the The National Intelligencer Newspaper collection, 1804-1844 MS2128
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- National Intelligencer, 1826 January 31 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 February 9 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 February 11 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 February 28 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 7 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 7 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 9 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 11 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 14 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 16 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 21 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 23 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 March 28 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 April 6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 April 8 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 April 18 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 April 29 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 May 23 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 8 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 13 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 22 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 24 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 6 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 13 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 18 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 20 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 July 22 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 August 15 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- National Intelligencer, 1826 December 19 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- National Intelligencer, 07/31/1827 (Box 3, Folder 216)
- National Intelligencer, 08/29/1827 (Box 3, Folder 217)
- National Intelligencer, 10/20/1827 (Box 3, Folder 218)
- National Intelligencer, 11/28/1827 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- National Intelligencer, 01/24/1828 (Box 3, Folder 220)
- National Intelligencer, 04/05/1828 (Box 3, Folder 221)
- National Intelligencer, 04/08/1828 (Box 3, Folder 222)
- National Intelligencer, 05/06/1828 (Box 3, Folder 223)
- National Intelligencer, 05/08/1828 (Box 3, Folder 224)
- National Intelligencer, 06/07/1828 (Box 3, Folder 225)
- National Intelligencer, 07/03/1828 (Box 3, Folder 226)
- National Intelligencer, 07/29/1828 (Box 3, Folder 227)
- National Intelligencer, 09/20/1828 (Box 3, Folder 228)
- National Intelligencer, 12/13/1828 (Box 3, Folder 229)
- National Intelligencer, 12/23/1828 (Box 3, Folder 230)
- National Intelligencer, 01/10/1829 (Box 3, Folder 231)
- National Intelligencer, 01/29/1829 (Box 3, Folder 232)
- National Intelligencer, 01/03/1829 (Box 3, Folder 233)
- National Intelligencer, 01/28/1829 (Box 3, Folder 234)
- National Intelligencer, 01/19/1829 (Box 3, Folder 236)
- National Intelligencer, 05/19/1829 (Box 3, Folder 237)
- National Intelligencer, 05/21/1829 (Box 3, Folder 238)
- National Intelligencer, 06/01/1829 (Box 3, Folder 239)
- National Intelligencer, 06/11/1829 (Box 3, Folder 240)
- National Intelligencer, 07/01/1829 (Box 3, Folder 241)
- National Intelligencer, 07/16/1829 (Box 3, Folder 242)
- National Intelligencer, 08/03/1829 (Box 3, Folder 243)
- National Intelligencer, 08/06/1829 (Box 3, Folder 244)
- National Intelligencer, 08/13/1829 (Box 3, Folder 245)
- National Intelligencer, 11/12/1829 (Box 3, Folder 246)
- National Intelligencer, 11/16/1829 (Box 3, Folder 247)
- National Intelligencer, 11/23/1829 (Box 3, Folder 248)
- National Intelligencer, 1830 December 21 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- National Intelligencer, 01/10/1832 (Box 3, Folder 249)
- National Intelligencer, 11/14/1832 (Box 3, Folder 250)
- National Intelligencer, 11/17/1832 (Box 3, Folder 251)
- National Intelligencer, 12/11/1832 (Box 3, Folder 252)
- National Intelligencer, 04/01/1833 (Box 3, Folder 253)
- National Intelligencer, 04/30/1833 (Box 3, Folder 254)
- National Intelligencer, 06/06/1833 (Box 3, Folder 255)
- National Intelligencer, 08/10/1833 (Box 3, Folder 256)
- National Intelligencer, 07/10/1834 (Box 3, Folder 257)
- National Intelligencer, 07/17/1834 (Box 3, Folder 258)
- National Intelligencer, 10/29/1834 (Box 3, Folder 259)
- National Intelligencer, 12/11/1834 (Box 3, Folder 260)
- National Intelligencer, 12/18/1834 (Box 3, Folder 261)
- National Intelligencer, 01/17/1835 (Box 3, Folder 262)
- National Intelligencer, 04/04/1835 (Box 3, Folder 263)
- National Intelligencer, 05/21/1835 (Box 3, Folder 264)
- National Intelligencer, 05/26/1835 (Box 3, Folder 265)
- National Intelligencer, 03/15/1836 (Box 3, Folder 266)
- National Intelligencer, 11/09/1836 (Box 3, Folder 267)
- National Intelligencer, 12/10/1836 (Box 3, Folder 268)
- National Intelligencer, 12/13/1836 (Box 3, Folder 269)
- National Intelligencer, 08/05/1837 (Box 3, Folder 270)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1838 (Box 3, Folder 271)
- National Intelligencer, 01/20/1838 (Box 3, Folder 272)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1838 (Box 3, Folder 273)
- National Intelligencer, 01/08/1838 (Box 3, Folder 274)
- National Intelligencer, 04/16/1838 (Box 3, Folder 275)
- National Intelligencer, 05/08/1838 (Box 3, Folder 276)
- National Intelligencer, 06/09/1838 (Box 3, Folder 277)
- National Intelligencer, 06/12/1838 (Box 3, Folder 278)
- National Intelligencer, 09/29/1838 (Box 3, Folder 279)
- National Intelligencer, 10/10/1838 (Box 3, Folder 280)
- National Intelligencer, 10/24/1838 (Box 3, Folder 281)
- National Intelligencer, 01/22/1839 (Box 3, Folder 282)
- National Intelligencer, 01/24/1839 (Box 3, Folder 283)
- National Intelligencer, 01/19/1839 (Box 3, Folder 284)
- National Intelligencer, 04/18/1839 (Box 3, Folder 285)
- National Intelligencer, 08/21/1839 (Box 3, Folder 286)
- National Intelligencer, 11/20/1839 (Box 3, Folder 287)
- National Intelligencer, 01/01/1840 (Box 3, Folder 288)
- National Intelligencer, 04/07/1840 (Box 3, Folder 289)
- National Intelligencer, 04/21/1840 (Box 3, Folder 290)
- National Intelligencer, 04/03/1841 (Box 3, Folder 291)
- National Intelligencer, 06/19/1841 (Box 3, Folder 292)
- National Intelligencer, 09/11/1841 (Box 3, Folder 293)
- National Intelligencer, 10/30/1841 (Box 3, Folder 294)
- National Intelligencer, 03/15/1841 (Box 3, Folder 295)
- National Intelligencer, 03/26/1841 (Box 3, Folder 296)
- National Intelligencer, 04/08/1843 (Box 3, Folder 297)
- National Intelligencer, 06/05/1844 (Box 3, Folder 298)